Contact

webdeb@med.umich.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/deb-lee-phdrn-fnp-acnp-bc-chse-a6ab0180 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

BLS

Nursing Education

Deb Lee PhD, RN, FNP, ACNP-BC, CHSE

CLC Director at University of Michigan School of Nursing Marshall, Michigan

Summary

Experienced Clinical Instructor with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Patient Advocacy, Nursing Education, Pediatrics, and Life Support. Strong healthcare services professional with a PhD focused in Nursing Science from Michigan State University.

Experience

University of Michigan
CLC Director
April 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Ann Arbor, Michigan

University of Michigan Health System 6 years 10 months Clinical Instructor AGACNP Program September 2013 - Present (6 years 10 months) Ann Arbor, MI

Acute Care Nurse Practitioner CVC-ICU
October 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 3 months)

Borgess Health
Acute Care Nurse Practitioner
September 2010 - Present (9 years 10 months)

Borgess Medical Center
Director of Rapid Response
July 2010 - August 2013 (3 years 2 months)

Education

Michigan State University

PhD, Nursing Science · (2014 - 2020)

Rush University

Post Master's Acute Care Nurse Practitioner Certificate, Critical Care Nursing · (2011 - 2012)

Michigan State University

Family Nurse Practitioner Program, Nursing Practice · (2007 - 2010)

University of Michigan

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1992 - 1995)